Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little
more To get to the answers we're
looking for We came to this new world
believing That surely someday we
just might find the way All the
pieces of our dreams have now come
together Our bonds won't waver With
our dreaming hand Let's head on towards
A bright new future Now
everybody lift your hands up
Sing about what you are dreaming
Always stand up Raise up
the flag that you believe in
Gotta keep up We'll get past
everyone that's in our way
Let's head on never stopping
Only look up Keep your head up, way up
high Always step up If waves are rough,
jump to the sky Never give up Our wishes,
they will come together And
lead us on for the future
We drift on riding the
waves Towards another
shore day by day There are many meetings,
many goodbyes Underneath the flag we fly
I'll remember the pain within I'll keep
it in my heart forever And never take it
lightly But I won't surrender This freedom
I will keep in mind I'll keep holding on,
never stop it Now everybody
lift your hands up Sing
about what you are dreaming
Always stand up Raise
up the flag that you believe
in Gotta keep up We'll
get past everyone that's
in our way Let's head on,
never stop it
Only look up, keep your head
up way up high Always step up,
if brains are rough, jump
to the sky Never give up,
our wishes they will come together
And lead us on for the future
Hands up
Hey, let us in, you bastards!
Return Smoker and Tashigi
to us or out! What the?
An airship?
Come, come, children, follow me.
You're back home now, safe and sound.
Don't ever run off and make
me worry like that again.
Yes, thank you, master.
Yes, Master.
Give me the candy now.
Master, I want the candy.
Give it to me.
It hurts so much.
Master, I need the candy.
Of course, children.
You can have it right away.
First things first,
you just need to follow the friendly men
in the funny suits back
to the biscuit room.
I've left enough candy in there
to stuff your bellies full.
Sound good?
I'm going to my science lab now,
but I'll see you all very soon.
everyone behave yourselves and
toddle off to your room and eat as
much of the yummy candy as you want
let's go take us to our room mr.
sheet man sure kids follow me all
right listen up once you get them all
inside you lock that door tight And
don't ever let them get out again,
or they'll be hell to pay.
Of course, sir.
This place, it's scary.
Hey, what's wrong with
you, you little br -
I mean, little princess.
Cheer up now.
Don't you want to go back to your room?
You better hurry so the other kids
don't eat all the sweet candy.
Whoa, what the -
He's a bad guy, okay?
He's gonna put you in that
lab and never let you go!
Out of my way!
Who's up?
Master, give me the candy!
There you go.
Come along, children.
I'll take good care of you.
Don't listen to a word he says!
He's trying to trick you!
Don't you want to go home?
No! Help me out! I want to leave!
Huh?
Don't be crazy, kid.
It's freezing out there and we're
not even on the ground floor.
Now, go back to your room.
No!
Please save me, Nami!
Mocha? Hey!
Quit slowing us down!
I want the candy!
This is some kind of
punishment for being bad?
I see now!
I should have listened
to what they told me!
I'm so sorry!
Please help me!
I promise I'll be good!
Knock it off!
Get away from the door!
Dammit!
What a royal pain in the ass!
Please save me!
I'm sorry!
Please stop me!
Ow!
Can't believe I'm alive.
Poor Sanji's body is all banged
up and bloody, but still,
I'm grateful it's so resilient.
Foo's up!
Hang in there!
Can you hear me?
You brought me back
from the brink of death.
Thanks, Sanji.
It's not me, moron!
Hey!
Try not to sound so disappointed!
Hello, Vergo.
Sorry for the wait. Not a problem.
I've been snacking on coffee and cookies.
Strange.
Did I eat all the cookies?
There were no cookies.
Just coffee.
Oh, that's right.
I guess I wasn't snacking on cookies.
How much longer until
the experiment begins?
Soon, I hope. Very soon.
Monet, the video, please. Of course.
By the way, can't you do
something about your men?
I wish you'd keep them on a tighter leash.
Honestly,
I broke into a cold sweat when I realized
Smoker had set foot on my island.
Well, he's like a wild dog.
There's no leash tight enough.
So you say.
But I find that Sea Prism's stone works.
Oh, Law, you look fetching
in chains. So grim.
Well, it must have been upsetting to realize
you were helpless against Vergo, right?
The little deal we struck worked
out quite handsomely for me
So I'll allow you to stay on my island and
in exchange you'll
provide my men with legs
And I'd like to add one more condition.
You see
Simply put you're more powerful than
I am and to be frank that makes me
nervous I am the boss of this island
after all so if you wish to stay here.
I'm gonna need some insurance I have
no intention of causing you harm.
Whatever you need, I'll
do it well then. Law?
How does this sound to you?
I'm sure you noticed my dear
secretary Monet sitting over there.
I will entrust you with her heart.
Monet understood, yes, fine with me.
And in exchange, I hold on to
your heart for safekeeping.
What do you say?
Do we have ourselves a deal this way?
We both have each other
by the figurative throat;
it ensures that you won't try anything
funny and allows me to rest easy.
It's always a bad idea to
put your trust in others.
Well, you reap what you sow, right?
A tough lesson for you to learn, no doubt.
If you're worried about your heart,
Vergo's taking good care of it.
Hey, I know you're a rather shrewd man,
but you never thought to
worry about my secretary.
Needless to say, she's not
the woman you thought she was,
and she overheard your entire plan.
Crap, you okay man?
Traffic, I know exactly what
you were plotting against me!
I'm so disappointed law really here.
I had gone and convinced myself
that I had finally found a friend
So you clever secretary
saved your hide, huh?
Well fine.
I could admit that I should have
been wary of her that one's on
me I just didn't expect someone so
smart to work for such a dumbass
watch what you say to me forest fool
you're kind of amazing he took your
heart and you're still alive undone by
your own powers huh that is some record
-breaking stupidity pathetic what the
hell did you do with mine oh do you mean
this heart here poor smoke master i've
pulled up the video
Just as you instructed.
Really?
Luck is on your side, smoker.
All right.
Let's see it.
Hey, there's something projected up there.
The hell's that thing?
Where is it?
It looks like it's candy.
A huge piece of candy.
Greetings, unlawful brokers.
Thanks for tuning in.
A horde of fragmented Smilies are
currently on route from the Burning Lands.
And soon enough, they will all converge
here at this central point of the Ice Lands.
Upon this happy reunion,
they will all merge into one.
When they do, we'll have one
lovely Smiley, huge and deadly.
Then our experiment will begin.
You see, my Smiley, he's the living
incarnation of the toxic H2S gas.
In fact, I've already
utilized Smiley once before,
four years ago, to kill this island.
There was one problem with my last test.
Although they were saturated with poison,
my weakened subjects were
still able to evacuate.
Now this time, I've
devised a helpful remedy.
A bit of a boost.
A special meal to stimulate
Smiley's toxic form.
It provides an added effect to
his poisonous composition one
that will transform him into a
perfect weapon of mass destruction.
You're about to witness the birth of a new
weapon one that I call land of the dead.
They're right behind us—is it even
possible to outrun these damn things?
It's
gaining on us.
Ah,
crap, it looks like it's
finished forming into one blob.
Perchance, one of you could
explain this beast to me?
me What is it?
What difference does it make?
Just keep running
Do you guys see that?
Am I hallucinating for fatigue?
Is that a piece of candy?
Seriously, how dumb can this day get?
There's people down there, beneath it!
Master, we have visual of a
large, gelatinous creature.
I've got a feeling it's Smiley.
We're preparing the video.
We'll project the feed
onto the fog as planned.
Perfect.
Clear the area once you're done,
and you'll want to do it quickly because
it's about to get dangerous out there.
The dragon sled should do the trick.
something wrong what is that
we've got a problem there's some
chemical melting the sled it's
completely useless now we're stranded
how did this even happen where the hell
did this chemical come from it's eating
right through the what
oh my
that's
terrible
curses i'm so worried for your safety
not convincing listen to me you'll
have to run for it your suits
won't protect you and they'll just
slow you down quickly take them
off and then run to the lab as
fast as you can what well if you
say He wants us to take off the
suit has the master ever been wrong.
He knows what he's talking
about now do as he says, right?
All right.
Here's hoping this works.
There's a huge floating face now—is
it the ghost of a giant well?
You quit getting distracted by other crap!
crap Just focus on running!
My sweet Smiley!
How I have longed to see your face!
After all these years!
That's right!
Oh, Smiley!
You remember me!
It's so good to see you again!
There's a special surprise for you!
A delicious snack! Not yet!
Wait, Smiley, hold on!
You must be patient for a moment!
There you go. Good boy. Obey me.
Remember that I'm your master.
Quest, I've told you to wait.
You and I have so much
catching up to do first.
There was that one time.
Remember?
Yes, it was four years ago.
Okay. Sure, okay.
I wanted you to eat it now.
Good boy.
Yeah, he's not listening
to a word you say.
Smiley ate it!
Swallowed the candy hole! It's happening!
Good boy, Smiley!
Now be reborn!
Show them all of your power!
What kind of ugly baby is
it going to be reborn as?
The most powerful weapon
of mass destruction ever.
Man, that is one big frog.
Yo, crap, it's making
all sorts of bad noises.
What's it doing?
I don't want to laugh.
Neither do I, but I
know it's something bad.
We just got to keep running until we
get to the lab like a master said.
Dammit, why'd that stupid
sled have to go and break?
It's not fair!
Please help us, master!
I got a bad feeling about
the way that thing's acting.
They're up that giant candy,
giving a spot of indigestion.
Quit speculating and run!
Have you not noticed the frantic
flight of the island's soldiers?
I assure you, nothing
good can come of this!
Yeah, my thoughts exactly!
You have made me so proud of
you, Smiley, until we meet again.
Now, be reborn and arise.
Become the ultimate
weapon, land of the dead.
Transform this island
into a lethal wasteland.
What's wrong with my legs?
What's it doing to me?
Someone help me!
Ahh!
It's poison gas!
Keep running!
Don't let it touch you!
I can't move my body!
It's like a statue!
Oh no! Oh no!
It's getting on us! Master!
Yes, the experiment is a success!
I have perfected an inescapable death.
No one walks away from this.
Although the poison from my last experiment
worked, there were still survivors.
They were ambulatory,
able to seek medical aid.
That was the problem.
I should have immobilized
them from the start.
This new gas smothers the
body in a shell like ash.
The toxins seep through the skin
and instantly paralyze the victim.
Behold the most effective
mass-manufactured massacre spread
my toxic death show this world
what a living hell looks like
This is pure madness
No!
I want to live!
They're freezing solid!
Hey, what is this crap?
It's like some kind of horror show.
All the ones that got wiped out, they
look like Caesar's freak show soldiers.
I'm just glad we're not
where that purple smoke is.
Actually, wait a sec.
Where do you think they're filming this?
I wonder, don't turn around
if you haven't figured it out.
No, that massacre happened
right behind us—help, master!
master
Oh crap if that stuff touches us,
we'll end up like them. We're doomed.
We're on an island We can't
outrun a cloud of death gas now,
I get it—they sealed up the lab so they
can keep the gas from getting inside.
Open the damn door, Caesar,
you heartless bastard!
I don't want to die on your Frozen Island.
Damn, damn it, damn you—let us in!
Crap, it's
about to catch up to us?
to us
If you fall behind,
we'll have to leave you!
Slow down and you're as good as dead!
Dino!
There's no way we can outrun it!
There's some kind of
large animal up ahead!
It looks like a giant lizard!
No, it's...
It's a dragon, a dragon, so it would
appear—don't give me that crap!
Dragons are from fairy tales.
They're real enough on this island,
but this one looks smaller
than the other one I saw.
Holy crap—we can fly on the damn thing!
If we catch it, that's a brilliant
idea—then let's do it and do it fast.
I can't keep running like this—wait
up, you fairy tale bastard!
you fairy tale bastard
Hey, that's Zoro!
They're all running from the smoke!
Would you look at those fools?
What are they doing out there?
And what the hell kind
of stupid run is that?
Oh, look, the samurai
got his whole body back.
Yeah, you're right!
Guess that means he's not
gonna give me his legs.
Hey, wait, that's not
important right now, Robin!
Run faster, guys!
That smoke will freeze you dead!
You gotta run!
Oh, man.
I don't have the strength to yell.
Damn it.
Don't see Prism Stone.
I take it those are friends
of yours, Straw Hat Luffy.
Well, that does help to explain
why they're so difficult to kill.
But their lungs will soon give out
and the gas will overtake them.
In a mere matter of minutes now, this
island will truly become a land of the dead.
Nothing can survive
outside of these walls.
Not one single soul will be left alive.
Oh, by the way, that includes you too.
What's happening?
and now I offer you all
as proof to the world:
evidence of the true
destructive power of my land.
of the Dead: a pirate
with 400 million berries,
a vice admiral of the navy, and
even a dreaded Warlord of the sea.
You're all completely helpless.
Against my genius tide of death!
What
do I do?
Think!
I've gotta do something or
he's gonna kill all my friends!
But how can I help?
With these injuries, I'll
only get myself captured!
And if that happens, the drug
formula and sedatives I found,
it'll all be for nothing!
Oh no!
I just don't know what to do!
I really don't need any
more close calls today!
Wait, what is this?
Don't do anything.
Who's through this?
Whoa, look who's inside!
It's Smokey!
It's Tashigi!
My goodness, they're still alive!
Uh, hang on.
They're all wrapped in chains! Damn it!
We really are all gonna
die! Smokey! That's Shoujou!
Guys!
They really built that lab.
As solid as a fortress, very true,
and rather well designed for
maneuvering heavy equipment.
How can you two be so relaxed?
How are we getting out of this jam?
I wasn't expecting Vergo
to show up, but no matter.
I'm not gonna let a small detail like
that hold us back now, Straw Hat—we're...
we're
sticking with the plan.
Just don't screw it up again.
Time for the counter-attack.